{
    "subject": "resource/Charlene_(song)",
    "predicate": "property/genre",
    "object": "resource/Soul_music",
    "human_readable": "The genre of the song Charlene is Soul music.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9577592611312866,
            "question": "Is Charlene a Soul music song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9288887977600098,
            "question": "What genre of music is the song Charlene?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8454156517982483,
            "question": "What is the musical genre associated with the song Charlene?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.756069540977478,
            "question": "What musical style defines the song Charlene?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7286685109138489,
            "question": "In what genre would you categorize the song Charlene?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7082359790802002,
            "question": "To what musical genre does Charlene belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6760627031326294,
            "question": "What type of music is Charlene classified as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6206809878349304,
            "question": "If you were to describe Charlene musically, what genre would you use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5880610346794128,
            "question": "What is the primary musical style of Charlene?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5330716967582703,
            "question": "Charlene's music falls under which category?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The genre of the song Charlene is Soul music.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1184_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary musical style of Charlene?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1184_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to describe Charlene musically, what genre would you use?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1184_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of music is Charlene classified as?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1184_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1184_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1184_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1184_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1184_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1184_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1184_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1184_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1184_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1184_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1184_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is my evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention Charlene as an R&B and Neo Soul musician, which implies that her genre is related to Soul music. Additionally, the text describes her music as soulful, soul-stirring, and having a timeless and modern sound that fuses genres like jazz, funk, and hip-hop with elements of R&B and Neo Soul. Therefore, it can be inferred that Charlene's music is indeed in the genre of Soul music."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents describe Charlene as an R&B and Neo Soul musician, which aligns with the statement that her genre is soul music."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}